ipm.edu.mo 2013-08-31

# MPI Web Site Privacy Policy Statement

**Web Site Privacy Statement**

Macau Polytechnic Institute respect personal data privacy, we promise to strictly implement the confidentiality guidelines when handling personal data and appropriately preserve the collected information. Macau Polytechnic Institute is committed to fully implementing and complying with the data protection principles and all relevant provisions of Law No. 8/2005 (Law of Protection of Personal Data) of Macau. This Statement outlines the information Macau Polytechnic Institute Web Site (hereinafter known as this Web Site) may collect and how that information may be used and processed.

If you have any enquiries about the above, please email us at [webadmin@ipm.edu.mo](mailto:webadmin@ipm.edu.mo)

**Collecting, Using and Handling of Non Personal Data**

When you visit the web site of Macau Polytechnic Institute (hereinafter known as this Web Site), we do not automatically record any information that can personally identify you, as well as collect any personal data such as name, address and etc.

When you visit this Web Site, our server will automatically gather the following generic information:  your IP address or domain name; the pages you access; the date and time of your visit; the type of browser you use and etc.  The purpose of recording this information is to track web browsing patterns and collate statistics about how this Web Site is being used for the sake of enhancing management.  No attempt will be made to identify users or their browsing activities except in the unlikely event of illegal activities, such as attacking this Web Site, our Institute could provide the recorded information to the law enforcement department to investigate and track down the misconduct individual(s) and handle due process of law.

**Collecting, Using and Handling of Personal Data**

If you provide personal details during your visit to this Web Site, we would only use and disclose your personal data for the purpose for which it was collected. We will not disclose your personal data to any third party or organizations outside our Institute without your consent unless otherwise stated, or required by law. If personal data is used in respect of research and statistical studies, no personally-identifiable information would be disclosed.

**Using of Cookies**

Generic information is collected through the use of “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to evaluate usage patterns, identify broken links and etc. so that we can improve both content and distribution. The configuration (if any) for this Web Site is not intended for collecting personally-identifiable information. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser or computer. However, doing so may restrict your ability to access some web pages.

**Change of Privacy Statement**

This Privacy Statement may update with changes to the laws and regulations of Macau and our Institution policies without prior notification. Please visit this Web Site regularly for the updates.

**Disclaimer**

The materials in this Web Site are provided for reference only.  Macau Polytechnic Institute shall not bear any legal liability for any error or omission of materials in this site.  Under no circumstances, shall Macau Polytechnic Institute be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss that result from the use of, or the inability to use, the materials in this site. 

Any information that is disclosed in network communications may associate with a risk of becoming public information and maybe use by a third person without receiving consent from the user, therefore it is necessary to exercise caution when deciding to disclose one’s personal information in such places. The Institute shall not be responsible or liable for such risk.
